

# **Burak Tamince**

**Date of birth:** 10/07/2002 **Nationality:** Turkish

#### CONTACT

- 9
- 34930 Istanbul, Türkiye (Home)
- $\checkmark$ 
  - btamince@gmail.com
- https://buraktamince.net.tr/
- https://github.com/Athena65 (**Gith ub**)
- https://instagram.com/tmncburak
- https://stackoverflow.com/users/ 19648244/burak-tamince (StackO verflow)
- in <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/burak-tamince/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/burak-tamince/</a>

### **ABOUT ME**

I have been studying in Gedik University as a computer Engineer. I graduated from Kartal Anatolian Highschool. I'm into computer programing, object orianted programming, artifical intelligence development. When i do my job i do with my %100 potential, I do my best. Also in C and C# language a have 2 years of experience. I can make all my search using Translate extension in English documentation easily.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

12/02/2024 - CURRENT İstanbul, Türkiye

## **Programmer** Waytogo Digital Coaching Platform

- Making Back-End, Front-End, Database operations via PHP, MySQL, Moodle.
- Also for better Productivity we use Aigle SCRUM methodologies.

Address Sanayi, Cube Incubation, Teknopark Bulvarı, Pendik/İstanbul, 34930, İstanbul, Türkiye

09/08/2023 - CURRENT İstanbul, Türkiye

### **Developer of software** ARKHE

- <u>Image Processing</u> operations with python and opency for Unnamed Aerial Vehicle maden by Gedik University Students (<u>Gedik University Technology Team</u>)in past years.

01/11/2023 - 28/12/2023 İstanbul, Türkiye

## Softwre Support Intern Mobitek Marketing Group

- Dealing <u>SQL</u> Quieries of campaign of clients company.
- Import, Export Excel datas to e-commerce site using admin panel.

12/06/2023 - 14/07/2023 İstanbul, Türkiye

## **Programmer** İstanbul Gedik University Software Office

-Making E-Commerce Site with PHP Laravel for Learning purpose as INTERN.

18/07/2022 - 25/09/2022 İstanbul, Türkiye

# Software developer TOMYA Teknoloji A.Ş

- Making Back End Operations in <u>ASP .NET Core 3.1 , 6.0 Web API , SQL Server , Mongo DB</u> for learning purpose <u>as INTERN.</u>

**Address** Maslak Mah. Büyükdere Cad. Spine Tower No: 243/10, 34485 Sarıyer/İstanbul, 34485, İstanbul, Türkiye

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

12/10/2021 - CURRENT İstanbul, Türkiye

## Computer Engineer Istanbul Gedik University

**Address** Cumhuriyet, İlkbahar Sk. No:1, 34876 Kartal/İstanbul, 34876, İstanbul, Türkiye **Website** <a href="https://www.gedik.edu.tr">https://www.gedik.edu.tr</a>

#### LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Turkish

Other language(s):

**English** 

Listening B2 Spoken production B1
Reading B2 Spoken interaction B2
Writing B2

#### German

Listening A2 Spoken production A2
Reading A2 Spoken interaction A2
Writing A2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user